Kheel Center Collection of Oral Histories 6058 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Dempsey (Box 13, Folder 9)
- H.E. Gilbert (original) (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Oliver (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Hiltz (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Hiltz (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Parks (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Stewart, Donald H. (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Joseph E. Ludwig (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Anthony Papalla (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Nicholas J. Esposito (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Graves Frank Ray (Box 13, Folder 19)
- James B. Daley (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Carole Mushler (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Mary T. Beilby (Box 13, Folder 22)
- James H. Parker (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Margaret Robb (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Dorothy Gutenkauf (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Kenneth P. Wickman (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Hiram Bleeker (Box 13, Folder 27)
- William B. Rogers (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Richard Correnti (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Charles Poskanzer (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Alan D. Willsey (Box 13, Folder 31)
- William W. Taylor (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Ching, Cyrus OH 1000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Ching, Cyrus OH 1000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Ching, Cyrus OH 1000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Ching, Cyrus OH 1000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Ching, Cyrus OH 1000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Ching, Cyrus OH 1000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Ching, Cyrus OH 1000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Ching, Cyrus OH 1000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Ching, Cyrus OH 1000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Ching, Cyrus OH 1000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Ching, Mildred V. OH 1000 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- David Saposs, no. 1001 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Smith, Howard OH 1006 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- William J. Avrutis OH 1008 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Cohen, Wallace M. OH 1010 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Keyserling, Leon H. OH 1012 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Lichtenstein, Howard OH 1013 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  copy
- George J. Bott OH 1016 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Harry Brickman OH 1018 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Consedine, William R. OH 1019 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Cushman, Bernard OH 1020 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Glasser, Herbert R. OH 1021 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Hunt, A. Bruce OH 1022 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Vose, Owsley OH 1024 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Fields, Ogden W. OH 1025 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Gross, Ernest OH 1026 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Pratt, George O. OH 1028 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Levy, Philip OH 1027 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Emerson, T.I. OH 1093 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Handler, Milton OH 1041 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Kleinen, Frank M. OH 1095 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Maslow, Will OH 1042 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Murdock, Ray R. OH 1055 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Silverberg, Louis G. OH 1088 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Van Arkel, Gerhard P. OH 1053 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Cyrus S. Ching - Interview no. 1000 (Box 16)
  -- tape #1-#19 (25 cassettes) - use copy
- Mrs. Cyrus S. Ching - Interview no. 1000a -- 3/30/1970 (Box 17)
  use copy
- David Saposs - Interview no. 1001 (Box 18)
  -- tape #1-#2 (3 cassette) - use copy
- Charles Fahy - Interview no. 1003 (Box 19)
  -- tape #1-#2 (3 cassettes) -- use copy
- Edwin S. Smith - Interview no. 1004 (Box 20)
  -- tape #1-#2 (4 cassettes) -- use copy
- Joseph Warren Madden -- interview no. 1005 (Box 21)
  -- tape #1-#3 (8 cassettes) -- use copy
- Nathan Witt -- Interview no. 1007 (Box 22)
  -- tape #1-#2 (5 cassettes) -- use copy
- Wallace M. Cohen -- Interview no. 1010 -- (3/12/1969) (Box 23)
- Howard Lichtenstein -- Interview no. 1013, 1969 (Box 24)
  -- pt. I-II (5/19/1969) - (2 cassettes) -- use copy
- Harry Brickman -- Interview no. 1014 -- (3/18/1969) (Box 25)
- Benedict Wolf -- Interview no. 1015 (Box 26)
  -- tape #1-#2 -- (3 cassettes) -- use copy
- Benedict Wolf -- Interview no. 1015 (Box 27)
- Herbert R. Glaser -- Interview no. 1021 (Box 28)
  -- Pt. I-II (2 cassettes) -- use copy
- Lee Pressman; Ben Golden -- Interview no. 1023, 1969 (Box 29)
  -- (5/2/1969) (3 cassettes) -- use copy
- Owsley Vose -- Interview no. 1024, 1969 (Box 30)
  -- Pt. I-II -- (3/14/1969) (2 cassettes) -- use copy
- Gross -- Interview #1026, 1970 (Box 31)
  -- 3/24/1970 (3 cassettes) -- use copy
- Levy -- Interview #1027, 1969 (Box 32)
  -- 3/14/1969 (5 cassettes) -- use copy
- Pratt -- Interview #1028, 1970 (Box 33)
  -- 3/18/1970 (7 cassettes) -- use copy
- Somers -- Interview #1029, 1969 (Box 34)
  -- 3/20/1969 (3 cassettes) -- use copy
- Collins -- Interview #1030, 1970 (Box 35)
  -- 3/25/1970 (2 cassettes) -- use copy
- Grady -- Interview #1031 -- 4/2/1970 (Box 36)
- Johnson -- Interview #1032 -- 4/3/1970 (Box 37)
- Rogers -- Interview #1033 -- 3/24/1970 (Box 38)
- Wykle -- Interview #1034, 1970 (Box 39)
  -- 2/3/1970 (2 cassettes) -- use copy
- Catherwood -- Interview #1035, 1969 (Box 40)
  -- 3/6/1969, 3/22/1969 (6 cassettes) -- use copy
- Bethge -- Interview #1036, 1970 (Box 41)
  -- 4/29/1970 (2 cassettes) - use copy
- Donovan -- Interview #1037, 1970 (Box 42)
  -- 4/30/1970 (3 cassettes) -- use copy
- Kaufman -- Interview #1038, 1970 (Box 43)
  -- 6/15/1970 (2 cassettes) -- use copy
- Welch -- Interview #1039 -- 4/3/1970 (Box 44)
- Garrison -- Interview #1040, 1969 (Box 45)
  -- 12/22/1969 (3 cassettes) -- use copy
- Handler -- Interview #1041, 1970 (Box 46)
  -- 4/15/1970 (3 cassettes) -- use copy
- Maslow -- Interview #1042, 1970 (Box 47)
  -- 3/20/1970 (2 cassettes) -- use copy